gameplaysurveys.com 2014-06-26

# GamePlaySurveys.com

**GamePlaySurveys.com Privacy Policy**

GamePlaySurveys.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website and services.

GamePlaySurveys.com adheres to the principles set forth in the Safe Harbor framework as established by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personally identifiable information provided to GamePlaySurveys.com from the European Union.

What personally identifiable information does GamePlaySurveys.com collect from me?

GamePlaySurveys.com collects information in several ways from different parts of our network of websites.

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, GamePlaySurveys.com asks for your name, email address, zip code, household information and personal interests. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to GamePlaySurveys.com and you can access the various protected areas of the site.Also, if you contact GamePlaySurveys.com we may keep a record of that correspondence.Whenever GamePlaySurveys.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

What are cookies and how does GamePlaySurveys.com use them?

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, GamePlaySurveys.com may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. Some areas on GamePlaySurveys.com where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. This avoids you having to enter your login information many times in one day.

Who is collecting information and for what purpose?

GamePlaySurveys.com collects valuable information which assists in developing new products and services. When you are on a GamePlaySurveys.com site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with GamePlaySurveys.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than GamePlaySurveys.com -- or its parent company UnitedSample,Inc. , you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service.

Promotions that run on GamePlaySurveys.com may be sponsored by companies other than GamePlaySurveys.com or may be co-sponsored by GamePlaySurveys.com and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared.

Any Sensitive Information (i.e. personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual) will be treated with additional care. If GamePlaySurveys.com intends to disclose such information to a third party or use it for a different purpose than originally collected, then you will be expressly asked permission prior to any such disclosure.

Please be aware that GamePlaySurveys.com advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those websites linked to GamePlaySurveys.com are not covered by this privacy statement.

With whom does GamePlaySurveys.com share my information?

As a general rule, GamePlaySurveys.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. 

Please see the Terms of Service or User Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed.

**Business Partners & Sponsors:**

GamePlaySurveys.com may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If any personal data about you were ever to be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data.  
Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give GamePlaySurveys.com permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your email address will be shared. If more information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer.  
From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt-in to receive information from these third parties, GamePlaySurveys.com will (with your permission) share your name and email address with them.

**Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate:**

Under confidentiality agreements, GamePlaySurveys.com may match user information with third party data. Also, GamePlaySurveys.com discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 45% of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

Other: GamePlaySurveys.com may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating GamePlaySurveys.com ’s Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) GamePlaySurveys.com ’s rights or property, other GamePlaySurveys.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. GamePlaySurveys.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?

Only GamePlaySurveys.com (or agents working on behalf of GamePlaySurveys.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers.  
You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those GamePlaySurveys.com services that require registration in order to participate.  
GamePlaySurveys.com does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.

What is GamePlaySurveys.com ’s policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?

You may edit your GamePlaySurveys.com Account Information and your public GamePlaySurveys.com Profile at any time by using your GamePlaySurveys.com ID and password. If you have forgotten your password, please click here.  
Your GamePlaySurveys.com account can be deleted or deactivated.

Please contact [support@surveyhelpcenter.com](mailto:support@surveyhelpcenter.com) for further instructions about deleting or deactivating your GamePlaySurveys.com account.

What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?

Your GamePlaySurveys.com Account Information and GamePlaySurveys.com Profile are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. GamePlaySurveys.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your GamePlaySurveys.com account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.  
Whenever GamePlaySurveys.com handles personal information as described above, regardless of where this occurs, GamePlaySurveys.com takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, GamePlaySurveys.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

What else should I know about my privacy?

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Additional information**

Can I receive surveys on my mobile devices?

In addition to websites, some GamePlaySurveys.com surveys and solutions are offered via mobile devices. You will be participate in such surveys only to the extent you expressly agree to participate through this platform. You acknowledge and agree that in such circumstances, mobile tracking functions will be enabled which track your mobile device via position locators such as a Global Positioning System ("GPS") for the purpose of providing you with customized and timely surveys or related services and initiatives which are tailored to query and/or measure your specific preferences and/or opinions and to provide the most meaningful and timely information to GamePlaySurveys.com clients and partners. If, after participating in these offerings, you can elect to opt out at any time.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [support@surveyhelpcenter.com](mailto:support@surveyhelpcenter.com).
